National Mediation Board Emergency Board 180, Train Crew Consists 5579
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Mediation Board Emergency Board 180, Train Crew Consists
1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Emergency Board 180
5579
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Files of National Mediation Board Emergency Board #180.
5667671
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads -- United States.; United States. National Mediation Board; United States. National Mediation Board. Emergency Board 180
5667671
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of Clifford B. Alban Passenger Studies, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Detroit Studies Introduction and Statement of W. D. Murphy, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of Edward T. Harley Railroad Technological Developments, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Selected Difficult Runs Introduction and Jobs Summary Narratives, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Road Freight. Introduction and Job Summary Narratives, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Restudies of Runs not Reduced Under Arbitration. Award No. 282. Introduction and Jobs Summary Narratives, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Passenger Job Summary Narratives, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Source Documents. Negotiation and Mediation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of James H. Sharp. Experience of T.R.R.A., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of J.R. Wolfe. Experience of Chicago and Northwestern Railway, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of James N. Page. Summary of Moves of Buckeye Yard and Local Switching Crew. Statement of Ralph M. Decker. Switching in Industry with Radio Communications, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of Joseph A. Bonelli. Safety., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of Richard B. Hasselman., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Detroit Studies. Job Summary Narratives, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Train Crew Consist Rules in the Railroad Industry. A Historical Survey, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Other Typical Runs, Not Common to Detroit. Introduction and Job Summary Narratives, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16A, 16B)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of John J. Maher. Negotiation and Mediation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of Linton E. Ward. Method of Crew Study and Analysis, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of James H. Sharp. Experience of T.R.R.A., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Qualifications of Observers, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Before the Emergency Board. Train Crew Time on Motion Studies (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Railway Accident and Casualty Experience, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Scope and Contents
  April 1972
- Emergency Board No. 180. Chicago and North Western Railway Experience with Reduced Crews. A Microcosm, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Crew Consist Factors and Railroad Operations, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of the Proceedings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Washington, DC. April 10 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of the Proceedings. Morning Session., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Washington, DC. April 11 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Abstract of Crew Consist Agreements as Contained in Employees' Exhibit Nos. 4 and 5, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of the Proceedings., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Washington, DC. April 12 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Washington, DC. April 19 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 181. Report to the President., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Washington, DC. April 30 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Excerpts from Report of Presidential Railroad Commission 1962., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Excerpts from Report of Presidential Commission 1962., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Excerpts from Emergency Board No. 154., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Excerpts from Emergency Board No. 154., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Excerpts from Award of Arbitration Board No. 282 and Opinion of Neutral Members., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Excerpts from Award of Arbitration Board No. 282 and Opinion of Neutral Members., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Washington, DC. April 14 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of the Proceedings., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Washington, DC. April 17 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Crew Consist Agreements by Collective Bargaining Since Award No. 282 and Subsequent to Agreements, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Crew Consist Agreements by Collective Bargaining since Award No. 282, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Crew Consist Agreements by Collective Bargaining since Award No. 282, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Washington, DC. April 18 1972. Noon Session.
- Emergency Board No. 180 Documents. Sent to Local Chairmen., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  May 1972
- Emergency Board No. 180. Brief for the United Transportation Union. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Washington, DC. April 13 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Brief of Parties and Report to President by Emergency Board No. 172, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Railway Management and Railway Safety., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings. Volume No. 9, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  April 20 1972.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings. Volume No. 11., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  May 1 1972
- Emergency Board No. 180. Supplement to Closing Argument of John H. Haley, Jr., on Behalf of UTU (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Supplement to Closing Argument of John H. Haley, Jr., on behalf of UTU (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Exhibits. Affidavit of John J. Maher., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  January 1965
- Emergency Railroad Resolution. Transcript of Proceedings., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  February 8 1973.
- Emergency Board No. 180. Reports, Statements, Exhibits and Agreements., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Detroit Studies., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Passenger., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Restudies of Runs not Reduced under Arbitration Award No. 282, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Selected Difficult Runs., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Other Typical Runs, not Common to Detroit, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Road Freight., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Detroit, Multi-Man Charts, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Emergency Board No. 180. Transcript of Proceedings. Volume No. 10., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  April 21 1972.
- Train Crew Consist Case. Award of Arbitration Board No. 282. Experience of the Former New York Central Railroad., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of James H. Sharp. Outside Industry Switching Practices., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Train Crew Consist Case. Statement of John L. Thompson. Operating Rules., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Documents and Correspondence Relating to Train Crew Consists, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Penn Central Transportation and United Transportation Union Documents, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  July 28 1972
- Reports and Agreements Pertaining to Penn Central Transport and UTU, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Penn Central Transportation Correspondence and Documents Concerning Compliance, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Proceedings for the Reorganization of Penn Central No. 70-347. Agreement. Report., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)